Guide to the Josiah K. Lilly Correspondence, 1931-1944 CAM.JKLCorr.2016
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- BL-BZ, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 974)
  Correspondence with Arlene Blackburn; Nelson Blackburn; Russell J. Blair; Roselyn Beam; Everette Beskirk; Zirian Blish; William Blombren; W.B. Bloss; Renee Blue; Bodley Book Shop; P.J. McGrath; William G. Boggs; Elorie Boll; Kenneth E. Boll; Ruth Bollbach; Esther Bollinger; Gene E. Bommhardt; Michael Bongo; J.O. Booker; Alton Booska; S.R. Boslet; Alice A. Bouden; Beecher S. Bowdish; Artie Bowen; Kathryn Marriott Bowlby; Richard Bowles; Ameda Jane Boyer; Marie Boyer; William E. Boyles; Wyman P. Boynton; Sara Lee Bracy; Henry Brady; Daniel F. Braen; Thomas W. Bramhall; Sara W. Brandon; H.G. Brannen; G.W. Brashears; Linda Braun; Elton Bray; H.K. Breckenridge; John Bregger; Clyde E. Brenton; Clyde C. Brenton; Karl B. Bretzfelder; Jefferson J. Brewer; A.C. Brice; Albert Brice; J.H. Bricker; Bille G. Bricker; J.H. Bricker; Helen S. Briggle; C.A. Briggle; Helen S. Briggle; Orren Briggs; N.B. Briscoe; S. Brithinee; Charles Brobst; Dora Brock; Arthur B. Briockless; Macy J. Bradie; Robert E. Brooke; Karl L. Brooks; John Willard Broom; Ken Broomell; J.B. Brower; Donald Brown; Donaldson Brown; Dorothy A. Brown; E.C. Brown; Edward C. Brown; Sedley Brown; H.V. Brown; Harold Brown; Mary Brown; Mildred Brown; Paul K. Brown; V.S. Brown; Brown University Library; Stanley Brozoski; Janice Bruck; F.E. Bruckmann; L.C. Bryan; Robert Bryan; Jane C. Bryce; R.H. Bryson; William Buchanan; Virginia Bucklew; Irene Buckley; Amy Bullard; Bulletin Index; Dorothy Bullock; William R. Bullock; Irise Burbage; Bob Burch; Usher L. Burdick; Gene Burger; Fred Ross Burgess; Ray H. Burley; Fred Burnham; Ethel Burns; Marion L. Burns; Waters F. Burrows; H.J. Burt; Millard P. Burt; Broward Busard; Carl R. Busch; Doris Bush; Frank A. Bush; George Bush; Eleanor H. Bussell; John E. Butler; Henry W. Butterfield; Mark Byron
- C, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 975)
  Correspondence with Ralph Cain; R.D. Calhoun; Robert Call; John R. Callahan; Lorena Callahan; R.D. Calhoun; Callely, Mary A.; Cameron, Carl E; Cameron, J.W.; Twila Camp; H.D. Campbell; Leslie Hinton Campbell; Mildred Campbell; Nelson Campbell; H.D. Campbell; Robert J. Campbell; Tom A. Campbell; John H. Cantrell; Joseph T. Caragher; Vincent S. Carberry; Lewis Corlew; Annette Carlin; E.C. Carlinc; E.R. Carlisle; Arthur B. Carlson; Patrick Carlton; Eldon E. Carman; Carol Carmichael; Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh; Elizabeth Carney; Lucie V. Carpenito; W. P. Carpenter; George W. Carroll; J.L. Carson; E.B.M. Casey; M. Celine; Central Drug Store; War Relocation Authority, Central Utah Project; Charles F. Ernst; Henry J. Certain; Louise Chadwick; Sidney Chalfant; Francis B. Chalifoux; John F. Chalker; Elmer R. Chamnes; Grace Chapin; Arthur L. Chapman; Bruce Chapman; Vita M. Chapman; Geneva Charette; M. Charles; Chartier, Thora; Chathan Towship School; Rhea Chedester; Ruth Chelnick; The University of Chicago; Emma Childs; W.B. Chilton; William D. Chrietzberg; Lund Christinsen; Ole Christianson; G.H. Christin; Henry Chura; S.H. Church; Samuel Harden Church; Ovideo Ciaccarini; Thomas Clark; Alden C. Clark; Joseph C. Clark; R.C. Clark; Thomas D. Clark; Tom Clark; George L. Clarke; John Clarke; James H. Clatworthy; Frances Cleary; Sister M. Clement; Irene Clemons; Daniel M. Clemson; Cleveland Public Library; Reginald E. Clevett; Wm. Clift; Reverend Kenneth Close; G.A. Coas; Theresa Cocca; Lola M. Coffeet; G.T. Coggswell; Sidney Cohen; Marlon Cohn; Charles N. Cole; Judsen Cole; Lucy Cole; J. Winston Coleman Jr.; Collectors Bookshop; College Book Exchange; Eleanor Reid; Byron Hone Collins; John R. Collison; Colorado River Relocation Project; Brace Conning; Frank Conway; Norma G. Conway; J.F. Conway; Robert Cook; T.C. Cook; Walter I. Cook; Gloria Cooke; Richard Cooke; Elizabeth Ruth Cooling; Madeline Cooney; N.R. Cooper; Katherine W. Copley; Dora Cordery; Carl Cordes; Valentine Cornelius; Dorothy Cornish; Forrest G. Cotton; R.M. Cowan; Henry Cowell; Vida W. Cowin; Dana L. Cox; Crawford A. Coy; Mary Coyle; Charles B. Craft; F.S. Craig; Helen M. Crane; Paul Crank; Gale Craven; A.E. Crawford; Sam U. Crawford; Sam U. Crawford; E.D. Crites; Phillip Lee Crittenden; Charles W. Crommett; H.K. Cronk; H.L. Crooks; W.D. Crooks; Henrietta Crosman; Daniel Culhane; Cumberland University; William H. Curran; Curtis Publishing Company; R.L. Cusac
- Republic Bank Note Co., 1941 (Box 25, Folder 976)
- D, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 977)
  Correspondence with Ida J. Dacus; Richard V. Daggett; Owen P. Daly; Frederick A. Danforth; George J. Welsh; Rebecca Daniel; William Danielczk; Isabel Dansiger; Dartmouth College Library; Elsie J. Dau; Mary Agner Daugherty; Davey C. Davies; Hilda M. Jean Davies; Albert T. Davis; Anna P. Davis; H.S. Davis; Harry Davis; Hemer F. Davis; Hugh D. Daivs; J.A. Davis; J. Bryan Davis; Kathleen M. Davis; Lucille Davis; Margaret Davis; Mildred Davis; Paul Davis; Paul F. Davis; Philip Davis; Sam W. Davis; Tom Pears, David and Warde, Inc; Emmett Davison; F.C. Day; Edward L. Dean; Carola Decker; Gilbert S. Decker; James V. Deegan; George Deering; Mary E. Deering; W.B. Delaporte; Hester J. Deller; Lios Demarest; Rose Demorest; Jackie Roekett Dempsey; John F. Dennigan; Peter Denning; James Dent; Clarence E. Dentler; Frank R. Denton; Denton, Contier and Daniels; Edward L. Denney; Edward L. Denny; Marie Dermitt; H.M. Dermitt; Civic Club of Allegheny County; Leo F. de Sola; R. Nathaniel Dett; K. Devlin; Robert H. Devlin; Chester De Vries; Elizabeth Dewey; Heyliger de Windt; L.A. De Wolfe; Harry Dichter; Paulyne Dick; Jack Dickens; Ruby Dickens; June Diehl; W.C. Dierks; David B. Dillehunt; David B. Dillehunt; K. Dinger; Gordon Dillon; C.W. Dinkins; Diorfman; Louis J. D'Ippolito; Frank Dobney; George Edward Dodd; jean Dodd; Mary Thornton Dodge; Robert E. Doherty; Louis A. Dole; Adette Dolhonde; M. Dolores; Dominican Sisters; Curtis J. Donley; T.C. Donovan; William Doolittle; Albert Dorr; Harry R. Dorr; Walter W. Dorwart; W.E. Dougherty; Lee Douglass; Robert B. Downe; L.J. Doyle; W.J. Doyle; J.F. Drake; Dravo Corporation; Dorothy Dravo; Morrill Drew; H.L. Dreyer; Bessie Driggers; M.L. Dryden; Richard Dryden; Arcady Dubensky; A.M. Dudley; Lynn B. Dudley; E.M. Duerbeck; Michael Dugas; Mary T. Dunn; P.O. Dunn; Paul O. Dunn; L.A. Dunscombe; Flyd R. Dunsworth; Cyrus W. Durgin; Patricia Durnin; George Dutt; Warren W. Dyer; Warren W. Dyer
- E, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 978)
  Correspondence with W.H. Eads; W.O. Boyd; Boyd Eagle; Ethel Eakin; Will Earhart; Dorothy C. Eastep; L.W. Easton; J.L. Eaton; Esther Edmundson; E.J. Edwards; W.M. Edwards; Henry Ehlers; Nina Jean Eicher; Lynn Eikel; Ruth Einhorn; Rudolf Elie; H.N. Elkins; Denson Ellerbee; Edward B. Ellis; Eleanor Ellis; Morris Ellison; Gertrude S. Ely; Howard U. Emmert; Grace Engel; James K. English; Enoch Pratt Free Library; Miriam R. Ephraim; John F. Epina; Geary Eppley; Hilda H. Erickson; Marion Erwin; Louise Escue; Charles W. Evans; George W. Evans; Ruth Evans; Thomas N. Evans; Jacob Evanson; Clay Everhard; Alice B. Ewing; Eye and Ear Hospital; Jane Ezelle
- F, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 979)
  Correspondence with Mary Fabian; Frederick Fairclough; A.M. Fairgrieve; Dale Fairman; Falk Clinic Hospital; Robert Farley; W.R. Farly; William R. Farmer; Alice V. Farnem; Alice V. Farnam; Frances Farran; Stephen T. Farrell; Stephen P. Farrill; Albert S. Faulk; Worth T. Faust; Wilhelmina Feaster; Charles W. Feinberg; Irving Feinberg; Milton Feitelson; Gerald Fenlon; Raymond J. Fenstermaker; C.W. Ferguson; Ruth Ferris; James McElroy Fetterman; Bert D. Fetzer; Mary Fidele; William Fields; Henry B. Figel; Joanne Finley; Frederick J. Finn; Carl Fischer, Inc.; H.P. Fischer; J. Fischer and Bro.; Joseph A. Fischer; M.J. Fish; Franklin D. Fishcer; Florence Fitch; Ada Florence Fitch; Fithian; John R. Fitzgerald; James H. Fitzgibbon; I. Fitzpatrick; John J. Fitzpatrick; R.G. Fitzpatrick; John Fitzsimons; Florence A. Flanagan; M.L. Fletcher; Flora Photo Co.; H.M. Flora; Annie Flower; Marion Flynn; James P. Foley; Ian Forbes; Evelyn Forney; B.S. Foster; Annie S. Foster; Catherine Foster; Ed Foster; Lorraine Foster; Richard Foster; Ruth Foster; Stanley Foster; William B. Foster; M. Francelle; Frances Miriam; M. Francilla; Florence Francis; N.P. Frandsen; C.J. Franklin; Nellie Freeman; Luther A. Freeman; Edwin M.C. French; G.Y. Frentzel; Glenna York Frentzel; Glenna York Frentzel; William Y. Frentzel; Paul F. Frese; Robert Fridenberg; Zurich Friedland; Anna Friedman; Arthur Friedman; C.H. Froelich; Charles Frohner; Ross Fulkerson; John M. Fulmer; George A. Furman
- FL-FO, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 980)
  Correspondence with Elmer W. Flaccus; John W. Flack; John W. Flack; W.L. Flanagan; Bernice T. Fleming; Lou Flemming; Len Flemming; F.W. Fletcher; Estelle Fliegel; Kendall H. Flint; Helen Flood; Florida State College for Women; Florida State Exhibit; Annie D. Flower; A.T. Floyd; H. Alen Floyd; Louise Flynn; Virginia Fogle; P.K. Foley; Jessie E. Foote; W. Cameron Forbes; Guy Stanton Ford; Fordham University; A.M. Foreman; Pauline Foreman; Margaret Forsyth; Fort Worth Public Library; Harry Emerson Fosdick; Ada Fosnaugh; Allison Foster; B.S. Foster; Bertha Foster; Eli C. Foster; Eugene Foster; Lorraine Foster; Richard Knowlson Foster; Sarah Elizabeth Foster; William B. Foster; William Trufant Foster; Ella Mae Foster; Annie McDuffie; Dan L. McTaggart; Margaret Sloan; Foster School; Dwight Fowler; Ila Earle Fowler; Andrew Fox; Ernest B. Fox
- G, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 981)
  Correspondence with Galanti, Joseph; Rose M. Gallagher; Harold W. Gammans; J.E. Gardner; Billy Garner; Florence Garrott; Tony Gatawakas; Harriet I. Gates; Henry Gates; Thomas V. Gates; Harvey B. Gaul; Rosemary M. Gelson; Claude S. George; Walter C. Germain; Tolman Gharst; Cora C. Gibbs; Esther Gibson; H.W. Gibson; Norman Gifford; Althea Gilbert; M. Gilbert; Robert Giles; Winifred Gilbert; J. Gordon Gilfillan; Randolph Gilman; Gaylord H. Gilmore; Marian Giltner; Ginn and Company; Joseph Ginsburg; Gloria Giordano; H.R. Githens; Kathryn V. Githens; Joseph Gladysz; George Gleeson; Mabelle Glenn; Etta I. Glick; Stanley J. Glowacki; Stanley T. Glowacki; Stuart Godfrey; N.C. Godsoe; Caroleen Goetting; John W. Goff; John W. Goff; W.B. Goggins; Alfred R. Goldman; Alfred R. Goldman; Edward P. Goldthwait; E. Louis Golladay; James C. Gompf; Martha A. Good; R.E. Good; William Good; Samuel P. Goode; W.F. Goodell; Marjorie Gordner; Jeanne Gordon; Sterling Gorgas; R.C. Gorham; Joseph F. Gossinger; Bert Gould; Rose Gouss; Government Printing Office; John H. Grady; Jean Graham; Madeline K. Graham; Marie M. Grall; George Granger; Maria Gratia; John M. Grayson; William F. Greavy; Edna May Green; George W. Green; John W. Green; William J. Greenan; Elizabeth S. Greene; James H. Greene; Virginia Greene; Harriett Fitch Greenwood; Thomas K. Greer; Gerard Greer; Gerald J. Greeve; Ernestine Grenier; J.R. Gress; Mary Griffenhagen; Ivor Griffith; Charles W. Grissom; Thelma I. Groner; Emma M. Groose; Joseph G. Grosch; Merle M. Grove; Thelma Grover; L.F. Gumbart; L.E. Gunther; Tracy Guthrie; Luis Guzman
- H-HAZ, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 982)
  Correspondence with Hackett, Loyce D.; Charles J. Haden; Charles Hadley; Gerard Haft; Elizabeth Hagberg; Dorothy Hagge; W.W. Hague; Jeanette Haines; Orley L. Haines; Hall of Fame; Charles S. Hall; G.C. Hall; George L. Hall; Donna Mae Halverson; Cary Hamilton; James C. Hamilton; Ramona Hamilton; Roland T. Hamilton; Ollie F. Hamm; Robert Hammer; F.E. Hammond; Larry F. Hammond; Francis E. Hand; Philip C. Henderson; Philip C. Handerson; W.C. Handy; Edmond Hanifan; Hanover College; John R. Hansing; Walter M. Hanson; Leora Harder; R.W. Harder; Herbert Hardesty; Jacqueline Harding; Robert C. Hardison; Arthur R. Hardwick; A.R. Hardwick; James W. Harelson; Edna L. Hargreaves; Leslie Harkness; Haskell W. Harr; Joseph W. Harrell; Mildred Harrington; Robert K. Harrington; Herbert E. Harris; Thomas E. Harris; Benjamin Harrison; Ethmer B. Harrison; Elmer B. Harrison; Wayne Harshaw; Delphine Hart; Ethel Hart; William Hart; Daniel J. Hartigan; Daniel J. Hartigan; M. Hartmann; Maurice M. Hartmann; Doris Jean Hartung; Lutie C. Hatwig; Freeda O. Hartzfeld; Freeda O. Hartzfeld; Julian H. Hatch; Lehman M. Hauger; J.J. Hawthorne; Florence E. Hazlett
- Houser, Louise, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 983)
  For letters to Louise Hauser before September 21, 1940, See "Inter Office Communications." Miss Hauser worked for the Foster Collection, separating and arranging newspaper clippings.
- HE-HY, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 984)
  Correspondence with The Clarion Republican; William Heazlett; George E. Hedger; George E. Hedger; Bert E. Hedrick; K. Page Hegner; Albert M. Hein; Cora Hein; Alice H. Henry; John P. Henry; L.K. Henry; Sam Henry; W.A. Henry; Geraldine Herman; Newton B. Barkley; Evelyn Herold; James F. Herrick; H.J. Herrmann; H.J. Herrmann; Rowena Herrmann; Maurice Herzberger; Charles Hess; Arthur L. Reynolds; C.J. Hickey; Richard Hickey; Williams J. Hickey; Theodore F. Hicks; O.C. Heistand; high School Library; Edward Hill; Fredrick T. Hill; Frederick F. Hill; Mark Hillery; Ellison Hillyer; Square W. Hilton; Doris Hinds; Betty Hipple; Ralph C. Hocker; Bradford H. Hodges; Fletcher Hodges; Francis T. Hodges; Charles Hoey; A.L. Hofer; Arthur H. Hoffman; E.H. Hoffpauir; Donald Hogan; Raymond P. Hogan; William H. Hogan; Fleta Mae Hohn; Franklin F. Holbrook; Herbert Holder; Herman Holl; James G. Holland; James G. Holland; Louise Hollenbach; Ruby Hollingsworth; Thelma Holloway; Henry Hotlzer; Miriam Holycross; Essie Hood; Irene Hook; Doris E. Hopkins; Ione B. Hopkins; Willie Hopper; Walter B. Horton; Paul E. Hozack; J.B. Houren; Laura M. Houston; Howard Ship Yards; Arthur Howard; Kathryn O. Howell; Kenneth G. Stowald; Willie F. Howell; A.W. Hudson; E.B. Hudson; Elizabeth Hudson; Roland Hueston; F.G. Hufford; Robert Hughes; Bernard L. Hughey; B.G. Hukill; Emory Hukill; Arthur B. Hull; Louise Humphreys; Lucile Humphreys; Ruth Hunsaker; B.L. Hunt; Hannah Hunt; Mary K. Hunt; Roy A. Hunt; Elizabeth Bardin Hunter; John Hunter; Ward Hunter; Thomas Hunter; Silas E. Hurin; Emmett Hurst; Paul W. Hurt; Paul W. Hurt; Lewis E. Huseman; Rachel Huston; Margaret Hutsko; Elliott J. Hymans
- Howard, John Tasker, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 985)
  Correspondence with John Tasker Howard of Glen Ridge, NJ. In 1932 Howard was a musicologist with one book to his credit. He earned additional income by lecturing around the country and hosting a radio show. Howard and Lilly met for the first time in Nov, 1932. By Dec. 1932 Howard was working on the Foster biography, receiving a small stipend from Lilly for support during his research. Howard was rapidly accepted by the Foster Hall staff. The biography was published in Jan. 1934. The correspondence during this year is rich with gossip as well as opinions and reviews of the many plays and movies which were being produced that season. Howard was having legal difficulties at this time. His publishers were withholding permission for Howard to dramatize the biography which he hoped to have Gene Raymond direct. The 1935-38 correspondence holds an enormous quantity of letters about the Foster house controversy, verification that Foster lived in Hoboken; Howard's arrangements of Foster songs; Maskell Ewing's death. Also a lot of notes between Howard and Hodges pointing out errors in the biography.
- Indianapolis Photo Co., 1942 (Box 25, Folder 986)
  This company did a good deal of work for the Hall; they photographed every important acquisition. These photos were often used in exhibitions or as illustrations in journal articles.
- J, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 987)
  Correspondence with C.J. Jackson; Clyde A. Jackstreet; Dale Jackson; Dennis Jackson; J.R. Jackson; Luella Jackson; Myles F. Jackson; Leo L. Jacobs; JoAnn Jacoby; Gladys H. Jaeckle; L.E. James; Warren H. James; Janesville Gazette; Janesville Public Library; Jean Marie; Stephen Jelinek; Vivian Jelks; Jenkins Music Company; J.K. Jennings; Thomas R. Jewett; Albert Johnson; Archie Johnson; Dorothy G. Johnson; Edwin Johnson; Helen P. Johnson; Isabel Johnson; Miriam K. Johnson; R.H. Johnson; D.E. Jones; E.E. Jones; Mary E. Jones; Thomas C. Jones; Minneapolis Public Library; Howard D. Jorgenson; G.E. Judd; Charles L. Juliana
- K, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 988)
  Correspondence with Dale Jackson; Edward J. Kaiser; Karl Kaiser; L.A. Kalassay; Dan J. Kane; Frances J. Kane; University of Kansas; Regis Kausler; Herman P. Kayser; Joseph E. Kelleher; Edward Kelly; Joe Kelly; John E. Kelly; George R. Kemp; Joseph V.T. Kempton; Don C. Kennedy; Don Kennedy; Joseph Kennedy; Hannis L. Kennedy; Agnetta F. Kerns; Agnetta F. Kerns; Patrick Kerns; Darwin Kerr; Erskin Kerr; Erskine Kerr; M. Kevin; Robert Keys; Ray Kiehl; Raymond A. Kiehl; Ray Kiehl; Jeanone Kindt; Clarence H. King; Julia V. King; Will C. King; Wm. Kinna; Colleen Jean Kirk; Bernice F. Kirkpatrick; Edward Kleinau; John H. Knickerbocher; D.H. Knight; Lee T. Knode; Clara J. Knoll; William J. Knowles; William F. Knox; Harry Kobialka; Phyllis J. Koenig; R.J. Koessler; George C. Koontz; Kopicki; Edward Korn; Henry Koropal; W.H. Krack; Charles B. Kraft; H.S. Kreiling; Laura K. Kreinbihl; Katherine Krinke; Mildred Kristof; Jesse B. Kritzer; J.B. Kritzer; Ernst C. Krohn; Stephen Krupinski; Elizabeth Kuhlo; Thomas J. Kunz; Bessie A. Kuster; James Kutz
- L, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 989)
  Correspondence with Flora W. L'Hominedieu; Jessie Labhard; Theodore Labhard; T.R. Lachman; Eugene J. Lacock; M. Lacritz; H.C. Ladirach; Fred Ladlow; E.C. Lafean; John E. Laine; H.C. Lake; Merton J. Lamb; Irene La Mont; Juan Lamurey; Ray Lane; Freda Langford; Charles W. Langstaff; Charles F. Lanning; Howard M. Laramy; Anna M. Larcom; Anne R. Larkin; Charlotte Larson; John Larson; National Catholic Community Service Club, Las Vegas, New Mexico; Harold S. Lavery; Dorothy Lawrence; R.H. Lawrence; William Lawton; Edith C. Lazear; Flora Lessie Lea; Leadbeater; Wilber H. Leadbitter; Ebenezer H. Learned; Corillia Leazer; Edward B. Lee; Will Le Grande; Wilds P. Lehr; Neomi Leiting; J.L. Lenert; Dick Lemen; John J. Lennon; Mary Lenore; Mary Lentine; Arthur R. Lenz; M. Leon; Leonard; Patricia Lesher; Josephine Letson; Calvin D. Leuthold; Lester Levy; Ralph Lewando; A.L. Lewin; Florence Lewis; Geth Lewis; Helen B. Lewis; Library of Congress; Leicester B. Holland; R. Lightfood; Doris Lile; Jean Lilley; Eli Lilly; J.K. Lilly; Ruth Lilly; Edgar Linch; Doris Lindenmuth; William B. Lindsly; A.S. Linhart; Betty Linn; Ruth L. Linn; Eloise Lisle; Frances E. Little; Jean Phylis Little; Lulu L. Little; Mildred Little; Enoch Livengood; Ensley M. Llewellyn; Leonard Lobe; Fred Lockley; M. Lois; H. Lows; H. Lones; Joseph H. Lones; Sascha London; Long Beach Public Library; Long Beach Press Telegram; Claude L. Long; Rose K. Longstreet; Los Angeles Public Library; Louisville and Nashville Railroad; Bobbie Jane Love; Edith Lowe; B. Lovenstein; Samuel M. Lovenstein; F.D. Lowe; Belvie R. Lowrance; William J. Flood; Charles H. Lowry; Jean Lowry; James B. Lowther; Lantina Lucchetti; Luce's Press Clipping Bureau; Anna C. Lufburrow; Robert W. Lull; Dorothy Lundeen; C.W. Lundgren; Frank Luther; Rose Lyles; Bertha L. Lyons; Mary Lytton
- Lilly, Josiah Kirby, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 990)
- Lilly (D.J. Black), 1942 (Box 25, Folder 991)
- M-MAZ, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 992)
  Correspondence with James Mace; Dan J. Macer; Michael Machlowitz; Curtis Maddlen; Thomas J. Madden; James Madison; John W. Madosh; Mary Antoinette Madsen; Magee Hospital; Charles Magner; Martha Maham; Doris Maier; George A. Makovic; Arthur H. Malloy; Catherine Malone; Ray Malott; Marian Maloy; Mae H. Malpass; William Malpass; Edward Manczuk; Rosylin Mandel; Beatrice Mangino; Larry J. Manion; Alfred Mann; M.D. Mannix; Manzanar War Relocation Area; William C. Maple; R.C. Marable; Thomas Marcell; Joseph O. Marcotte; Joseph E. Marcus; Marine Photo Company; Ruth Markouritz; Consuela Marie; A.J. Marino; John A. Marks; Samuel E. Marks; Marie Maronpot; Alfred L. Marriott; Dorothy Marslen; Joseph W. Marsh; A.P. Marshall; George M. Marshall; John C. Marshall; Arthur G. Martin; Charles Martin; Elizabeth D.V. Martin; J. Stephen Martin; Jack Martin; Margretto Martin; Roscoe B. Martin; S. Martin; Sally Martin; W.B. Martin; W.H. Martin; Ward Martindale; Reubin A. Martinson; Mary Alberta; Tom Masamori; Carroll W. Mason; James A. Mason; Robert J. Mason; Joseph L. Mastran; A.H. Mathias and Co.; Arthur E. Mathison; F.S. Matlack; Dolly Matters; Alvin M. Mavis; Marion A. Maxim; Lyle Maxwell; A.P. May; Mercedes Mayer; James T. Maynor; Geo. P. Mayo; Henry S. Mazer
- Mc, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 993)
  Correspondence with Walter Q. McAdams; Edgar M. McAllister; Ethel I. McCarthy; Thomas C. McCaslin; Carlyle W. McClellan; C.W. McClellan; Lincoln Memorial University; Stewart W. McClelland; William D. McClellan; E/H. McClelland; John B. McCliskey; John B. McCloskey; McCloy Company; A.C. McClurg and Company; Joseph Lyle McClorison; J.L. McCorison; C.A. McCurdy; William W. McCurdy; Agnes E. McCusker; C.D. McDaniel; Alleen McDonald; Howard MacDonald; Leo J. McDonald; M.B. McDonald; Thirza B. McDonald; Margaret MacDonald; Elizabeth MacFarlane; James R. Macfarlane; Jesse Macfarlane; Malcolm Fletcher Macfarlane; John J. McGann; McGill University; William R. McGlumpy; Dorothy McIlroy; Julie McIlvaine; William B. McIlvaine; John J. MacIntyre; Richard McIntyre; Marion S. McIntyre; Daniel L. McKnight; Paul V. McKinney; William McKinnis; L. McLean; Leslie McLean; Myrtie McMaster; Margaret McMinn; McMullin; McNamara; Jess McShane
- ME-MZ, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 994)
  Correspondence with Mlanchard W. Means; Simon S. Medlin; C.E. Meeder; Ralph Melady; Naurette Mellinger; Edward F. Melocchi; Menasha Junior Chamber of Comerce; Menasha Wisconsin; Ralph H. Mengel; Rush Memifee; Mary E. Mennig; Sisters of Mercy; Mercy Hospital; Mercy School of Nursing; Meredith Publishing Company; Barbara Merrell; LaDelle Merrem; Charles Ramage Mershon; Janoce Mesics; Ethel C. Meskill; Eli Messenger; Juliam Messner; Geraldine Meteer; Edwina Metz; Arthur R. Meyer; Charlotte Meyers; Emma Meyersburg; Dorothy Michler; M. Mickalak; Albert R. Middleton; Charles Milbauer; B.F. Milburn; James C. Miles; E.R. Miley; Christine Miles; Donald Miller; Dorothea Miller; Duncan Miller; Edith F. Miller; Elmer E. Miller; Ernest P. Miller; Fred H. Miller; Marilyn Miller; Maxine Miller; M.C. Miller; Mildred Miller; Stenling Miller; Gerald Milligan; Harold Milligan; Ala N. Mills; Hazel Mills; Minidoka War Relocation Project; Minneapolis Public Library; Kennon Minter; Anna Mitchell; Henry Mitchell; Vernon C. Mitchell; William H. Mitchell; Martha Mitze; David Mitzer; Lester Ramon Mohr; A. Moldenhauer; Montana State College Library; Helen Montague; Montefiore Hospital; John C. Moody; Rae Moody; Arthur C. Moore; Helen M. Moore; John Mason Moore; Nancy Lou Moore; William H. Moore; William S. Moorhead; Billy R. Moran; Charles E. Moran; Charlotte Mordecai; Hattie M. Morden; Virginia H. Moreland; Norma C. Morenz; Anna Ruth Morgan; Naomi Morgan; Warren D. Morgan; Gene Morlan; Jack C. Morris; Lawrence Morris; Robert Morris; Roger J. Morris; Ellen Morrison; L.Q. Morrison; Anna Morrow; Bernice Morrow; Carrie Moser; Benita Mssman; Betty Moyer; S. Moyerman; Edna Mueller; Joseph Muller; Edith Muller; F.W. Mullins; Howard Mumbauer; Ida De Munnno; David V. Murdoch; Elizabeth Murphy; John D. Murphy; Kenneth Murphy; Timothy T. Murphy; Charles A. Murray; Elsie Murray; Foster Murray; Musical Forecast; Anthony Muskas; Burton H. Mustin; Lee T. Muth; Charles M. Myers
- Morneweck, Evelyn Foster, 1942 (Box 25, Folder 995)